



Grzegorz Laszczyk

info@grzegorzlaszczyk.pl grzegorzlaszczyk.pl linkedin.com/in/greglas github.com/glaszczyk 609 405 805

Skills

Web development:

∃ HTML₅,

€ CSS₃,

Sass, Sass,

JS JavaScript,

Gulp,

iQuery,

Git,

RWD,

php PHP,

WordPress.

Adobe:

Ps Photoshop,

Ai Illustrator,

InDesign,

Operating systems:

É

Mac OS X,

Windows.

Computer graphic:

- · UI design;
- · Ux design fundamentals;
- · photo editing;
- · vector graphic, infographic;
- · Corporate Identity design.

Typography:

- · typesetting rules;
- · layout design;
- · book, magazine design.

Printing:

- · prepress;
- · printing techniques;
- · printing surfaces;
- · finishing techniques.

Fast learning.

Teaching skills.

Work in group.

Work organization.

Work on tight deadline.

English intermediate.

German basic.

I am an experienced designer. I found that most interesting part of my work is to solve problems. I'm very interested in Javascript and I believe being web-developer will give me many new, interesting challenges. My understanding of design together with need for consistent personal development and team working is something I would like to use in my work.

Education

July-August 2016 CodersLab, coding bootcamp – Junior Front-End Developer

2001–2003 School of Promotion and Advertising Promocja – Associate degree;

April-August 2002 in Media Bildung in Cologne – Training in graphic software for print;

1996–2001 University of Economics in Wrocław – Master of Arts, Management and Informatics.

Experience

November 2012 to now freelance graphic designer

2010-2012 cooperation with Landbrand

· design for print (guidebooks, folders, flyers, brochures).

2010–2012 cooperation with Agencja Rozwoju Gdyni

· design for print (folders, brochures).

2002–2011 inMedia Polska Sp. z o.o. – DTP i computer graphic instructor

- · trainings in Adobe CS (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign) more than 9000 hours of workshops, more than 1000 people;
- corporate materials design for print (albums, catalogs, brochures, folders, flyers, rollups etc.);
- training from printing problems for marketing team in Deichmann Poland;
- · Photoshop training for Archicom SA;
- · InDesign training for Phoenix Press Media Publishing House.

2006–2011 cooperation with Raabe Publishing House

- · drawings for physical education materials;
- · drawings for medical materials.

Hobby

Computer coding, UI & UX design, RPG games.

Typography book and modern typography.

Drawing urban sketching.

Books SF, fantasy, artists biography.

Sport skiing, kettlebells.

I hereby agree for processing my personal data, included in my job offer, for the purpose of recruitment (as defined in the Act of August 29, 1997 on the Protection of Personal Data (Journal of Laws No. 133, item 883).